

CONTACT ME

+971-501609226
ariyaportfolio24@gmail.com
Al Barsha A - Mall of The Emirates, Dubai.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Adobe Creative Suite
Adobe PhotoShop
Adobe Illustrator
Canva

MS Office etc...

CORE QULIFICATIONS

- ♦ Research design
- Concept development
- ♦ Digital image generation
- ♦ Website design
- ♦ Image manipulation
- ♦ 2D and 3D modeling
- ♦ Problem-solving
- Time management and multitasking

LANGUAGE'S

English
Hindi(be)
Malayalam (Be)
Tamil

ANDAL AARTHI

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

CAREER OBJECTIVES

Creative graphic designer with innovative ideas and a unique approach to visuals. More than 8 years of experience developing designs for print media, online websites, and advertising. Solid understanding of marketing principles and advertising techniques. Great attention to detail and a talent for creating memorable visual designs. Enthusiastic team player who is committed to delivering top results on time. Passion for keeping clients satisfied with each project.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017-2023 O I Worked as a Senior Graphic Designer at SUN DESIGN STUDIO in Namakkal.

- ✓ I Worked Strong base of knowledge and skill in all elements of design, visual layout, color and drawing techniques .
- ✓ Illustration Design, After Effect Design, Product Photography, Marital Photography, Business Promotions and Advertisement Designs, Typography etc...
- ✓ Ability to work methodically and meet deadlines.
- Familiarity with design software and technologies.

2012-2015 I Worked as a Junior Graphic Designer at SKY TECHNOLOGY in Chennai.

✓ I Worked on Creating Innovative Logo Design, Motion Graphics, Creative Pamphlet, Brochure Designs. it's all done about the client satisfaction.

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Study design briefs and determine requirements.
- Schedule projects and define budget constraints.
- Conceptualize visuals based on requirements.
- Prepare rough drafts and present ideas.
- **♦** Develop illustrations, logos and other designs using software or by hand.
- ◆ Use the appropriate colors and layouts for each graphic.
- Work with copywriters and creative director to produce final design.
- Test graphics across various media.
- Amend designs after feedback.
- ◆ Ensure final graphics and layouts are visually appealing and on-brand.

EDUCATIONAL QULIFICATION

Present

- Master of Science,
- Multimedia Major,
- **❖** ICAT Designs & Media College,
- Chennai.

2012

- Bachelor of Science,
- Computer Science Major,
- Periyar University,
- Salem.

2022 - 2023

I Completed Certificate Course Training Program on Website Design Technology & Digital Marketing Strategies at SKAP TECHNOLOGIES in Trichy.